CODING IS AWESOME

After trying to teach myself how to code for the last year or so via online courses such as Udemy I decided to quit retail to make a full time commitment to becoming a Web Developer. This has been one of the best decisions I have made! I am really excited to join a team of talented Developers and continue learning.

TECH SKILLS

- React
- React Native
- Firebase
- Node.js
- SCSS
- JavaScript ES6
- Ruby on Rails
- CSS3
- React
- jQuery

CONTACT DETAILS



0413969140



guanhua.ding.work@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/guanhuading/



www.github.com/WilliamDGH



@DGH_William

WWW.GUANHUADING.COM

BRISBANE, QLD | GOLD COAST, QLD

CHARACTERS

Active Listening
Self Motivated
Team Player
Problem Solving
Bilingual - English | Chinese

GUANHUA DING

WEB DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER IN THE MAKING

General Assembly Sydney | 2018 - Present

FINAL PROJECT

REACT | REACT NATIVE | FIREBASE | NODE.JS | DIALOGFLOW

Note taking app across multiply platforms.

GROUP PROJECT

REACT | FIREBASE | BOOTSTRAP

Online gaming room site for board game lovers. It was a challenge but also a great experience working with other developers.

MORE PROJECTS AND CODE SAMPLES ON GITHUB

STOCK SUPERVISOR

Tommy Hilfiger (PVH Brands Australia) | 2014 - 2018

- Assist store manager
- Acting as manager of the day
- · Prepare banking and stock documents

DELIVERY DRIVER

Domino's Pizza | 2013 - 2014

- Food preparation
- Food delivery

EDUCATION HISTORY

GENERAL ASSEMBLY SYDNEY

Web Development Immersive | 2018 - 2019

- JavaScript, CSS, HTML
- Ruby on Rails
- Git, GitHub, CLI
- Working with a team of developers

QUEENSLAND UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Diploma of Business | 2013 - 2014

- Accounting
- Marketing
- Economics
- Global Business
- Management